rafaytutorials.com 2014-03-31

# Privacy Policy | RafayTutorials

At [RafayTutorials](http://www.rafaytutorials.com/) the privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

Your privacy is very important to us. At [RafayTutorials](http://www.rafaytutorials.com/) we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

###  Website Visitors

Whenever you visit RafayTutorials, our web servers automatically collect logged information such as your TCP/IP address, data, time, and files accessed. This is part of our access logs which are kept for a certain period of time. These logs are used only for site administration and performance. We do not disclose these data to third party groups.

###  Cookies

Your browser is capable of storing "cookies" which will allow you to have a more interactive experience with RafayTutorials. By doing so, you allow us to assist you to customize our content to match your preferences and needs. However, cookies do not in any way disclose personal information, unless you voluntarily do so.

###  Personal Information

This is perhaps the most integral aspect of your privacy which may be exposed upon your use of our site. Personal information such as your name, email address, and contact details may be collected but only upon your own disclosure of these data. This may transpire through certain activities such as when you send us an email or when you complete some of our online forms.

###  Policy Revisions

In the case of any modification of our privacy policy, you will be immediately informed through email. Still, you must know that this will not alter how we handled previously collected personal information from you.
